{"questionBank":[
    {"id":1,"prompt":"Jupiter has over ____ known moons (pick closest answer)",
        "a":"561", "b":"79", "c":"206","d":"52", "answer": "b"},		
    {"id":2,"prompt":"What is the 5th letter in the alphabet?",
        "a":"d", "b":"f", "c":"g","d":"e", "answer": "d"},
    {"id":3,"prompt":"What is the correct way to do an alertbox in JS?",
        "a":"alert(“hello”);", "b":"box(hi);", "c":"superBox(“go”);","d":"alertbox(“goodbye”);", "answer": "a"},
    {"id":4,"prompt":"What does console.log(8+'9') put out to console?",
        "a":"17", "b":"16", "c":"8+9","d":"89", "answer": "d"},
    {"id":5,"prompt":"What is not a reserved word for Javascript?",
        "a":"interface", "b":"boolean", "c":"program","d":"throws", "answer": "c"},
    {"id":6,"prompt":"Javascript is scripting language that is ______ side",
        "a":"browser", "b":"server", "c":"executive","d":"none of the above", "answer": "a"},
    {"id":7,"prompt":"1st browser to support javascript was?",
        "a":"firefox", "b":"chrome", "c":"internet explorer","d":"Netscape", "answer": "d"},
    {"id":8,"prompt":"The Earth's diameter is closest to _______ miles long",
        "a":"16000", "b":"5220", "c":"7900","d":"88201", "answer": "c"},
    {"id":9,"prompt":"How do you call upon a function in javascript?",
        "a":"call Function;", "b":"!execute function()", "c":"function()","d":"function function()", "answer": "c"},
    {"id":10,"prompt":"How do you print to console?",
        "a":"console.out.print(hi)", "b":"console.log(12)", "c":"print(14)","d":"out.console(15)", "answer": "b"},
    {"id":11,"prompt":"?",
        "a":"", "b":"", "c":"","d":"", "answer": ""}
  ]}